###### Subscribe Us

 Subscribe

[

](https://www.alphr.com/)

[

](https://www.alphr.com/)

    [

    Xbox](https://www.alphr.com/category/video-games/gaming-devices/xbox/) [

    Nintendo](https://www.alphr.com/category/video-games/gaming-devices/nintendo/) [

    PlayStation](https://www.alphr.com/category/video-games/gaming-devices/playstation/) [

    Twitch](https://www.alphr.com/category/video-games/gaming-social/twitch/) [

    Discord](https://www.alphr.com/category/video-games/gaming-social/discord/) [

    Minecraft](https://www.alphr.com/category/video-games/games/minecraft/) [

    Steam](https://www.alphr.com/category/video-games/gaming-social/steam/)

 Search

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: September 20, 2023

Alphr (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the Alphr website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.alphr.com

Information Collection And Use
------------------------------

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address

Advertising
-----------

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a Raptive (“Raptive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Raptive will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Raptive’s data usage, click here: [https://raptive.com/creator-advertising-privacy-statement/](https://raptive.com/creator-advertising-privacy-statement/)

Log Data
--------

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie
-----------------------------------

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service.

Cookies
-------

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Service Providers
-----------------

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Security
--------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links To Other Sites
--------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.

Compliance With Laws
--------------------

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.

Changes To This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

### Search

Most Popular
------------

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on July 26, 2024

8 Ways to Optimize Microsoft Edge for Slower Computers](https://www.alphr.com/optimize-microsoft-edge-for-slower-computers/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on July 25, 2024

7 Ways to Customize the Windows 11 Notepad App](https://www.alphr.com/customize-windows-11-notepad-app/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on July 16, 2024

Chrome vs. Edge vs. Firefox vs. Vivaldi: Which Browser Is Better?](https://www.alphr.com/chrome-vs-edge-vs-firefox-vs-vivaldi/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on July 9, 2024

How to Merge and Center in Excel Without Losing Sorting and Selection Features](https://www.alphr.com/merge-and-center-in-excel-without-losing-sorting-selection/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on June 7, 2024

7 Brave Features You Will Not Find in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox](https://www.alphr.com/best-brave-features/)

[

Posted by Dave Johnson on June 4, 2024

What Does Clock Icon Mean on WhatsApp and How to Get Rid Of It](https://www.alphr.com/what-does-clock-icon-mean-on-whatsapp/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on June 1, 2024

How to Run AI Models Locally on Windows Without Internet](https://www.alphr.com/run-ai-models-locally-on-windows-without-internet/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on May 30, 2024

How to Use Gemini Mentions to Enhance the Prompt Experience](https://www.alphr.com/how-to-use-gemini-mentions/)

[

Posted by Mehvish Mushtaq on May 20, 2024

How to Put a Picture on Top of Another Picture on Instagram Story](https://www.alphr.com/put-a-picture-on-another-picture-in-instagram-story/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on May 15, 2024

How to Reply to All Social Media Comments With AI](https://www.alphr.com/reply-to-all-social-media-comments-with-ai/)

[

Posted by Mehvish Mushtaq on May 11, 2024

How to Put Full Picture on WhatsApp Profile](https://www.alphr.com/put-full-picture-on-whatsapp-profile/)

[

Posted by Mehvish Mushtaq on May 6, 2024

What Happens When You Remove Someone From Instagram or WhatsApp Group Chat](https://www.alphr.com/what-happens-remove-someone-from-instagram-or-whatsapp-group/)

[

Posted by Afam Onyimadu on May 1, 2024

How to Watch the UEFA Champions League Semi-Finals](https://www.alphr.com/how-to-watch-the-uefa-champions-league-semi-finals/)

[

Posted by Will on August 2, 2021

Managing the Hosts file in](https://www.alphr.com/hosts-file-windows-10/)

[

](https://www.alphr.com/)

* [
    
    ](https://www.facebook.com/alphrdotcom/ "Facebook")
* [
    
    ](https://twitter.com/alphr "Twitter")

###### Categories

###### Latest

Afam Onyimadu July 26, 2024

Afam Onyimadu July 25, 2024

[Chrome vs. Edge vs. Firefox vs. Vivaldi: Which Browser Is Better?](https://www.alphr.com/chrome-vs-edge-vs-firefox-vs-vivaldi/)

Afam Onyimadu July 16, 2024

[How to Merge and Center in Excel Without Losing Sorting and Selection Features](https://www.alphr.com/merge-and-center-in-excel-without-losing-sorting-selection/)

Afam Onyimadu July 9, 2024

[7 Brave Features You Will Not Find in Chrome, Edge, and Firefox](https://www.alphr.com/best-brave-features/)

Afam Onyimadu June 7, 2024

[What Does Clock Icon Mean on WhatsApp and How to Get Rid Of It](https://www.alphr.com/what-does-clock-icon-mean-on-whatsapp/)

Dave Johnson June 4, 2024

Afam Onyimadu June 1, 2024

Afam Onyimadu May 30, 2024

[How to Put a Picture on Top of Another Picture on Instagram Story](https://www.alphr.com/put-a-picture-on-another-picture-in-instagram-story/)

Mehvish Mushtaq May 20, 2024

Afam Onyimadu May 15, 2024

Mehvish Mushtaq May 11, 2024

[What Happens When You Remove Someone From Instagram or WhatsApp Group Chat](https://www.alphr.com/what-happens-remove-someone-from-instagram-or-whatsapp-group/)

Mehvish Mushtaq May 6, 2024

Afam Onyimadu May 1, 2024

© Guiding Tech Media 2024

[About Us](https://www.alphr.com/about-alphr/) | [Contact Us](https://www.alphr.com/contact-us/) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.alphr.com/privacy-policy/) | [TOS](https://www.alphr.com/tos/) | All Rights Reserved
